<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Emindfully</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string name="logo_name">Purpose</string>
    <string name="logo_des">An app to simple and healthy recipes with its practice on mindful eating.</string>
    <string name="logo_description">Explore a variety of recipes and the concept of eating mindfully.\nEating mindfully can be described as the practice of cultivating an open-minded awareness of how food preparation, eating environments and the food we choose to eat affects ones body, feelings, mind, and the environment around us.
    \n\n Here are 7 steps to eating mindfully:\n 1. Slow down the pace at which you eat.For example, take breaks during bites, eat more slowly, and take a break to breath.
    \n 2. Eat away from distractions, such as the TV, computer, or eating with phone at hand.
    \n\n 3. Become aware of your body state, letting you know when its hungry and full so you can recognise hunger cues more easily.
    \n 4. Use your hunger cues to guide your decisions on when to begin and end eating.
    \n\n 5. Choose to eat foods that are pleasing and nourishing by using your five senses(smell, taste, sight, sound, and touch) while eating.
    \n 6. Understand your motivations - eating foods that are emotionally comforting vs. eating foods that are nutritionally healthy.
    \n\n 7. Prepare your own meals where possible. The act of preparing food - touching, tasting and smelling - will help to improve your psychological relationship with food.\n </string>

    <string name="bowl_name">Acai Goodness</string>
    <string name="bowl_des">A fruit packed acai bowl.Topped with berries, strawberries, bananas, and coconut shreds.</string>
    <string name="bowl_description">Ingredients:\n 2 packets unsweetened frozen acai.\n 1 cup coconut milk.\n 1 cup frozen mixed berries.\n 2 bananas.
    \n\n Toppings:\n Mixed berries.\n Kuwait.\n Bananas.\n Coconut flakes.\n\n Method:\n 1. Place all the ingredients together in a high-powered blender
        \n and blend until smooth.\n
        2.Pour into desired bowls and top with mixed fruit and toppings. </string>

    <string name="juice_name">Pineapple Power</string>
    <string name="juice_des">A friendly and fruity combination of tropical variants and refreshing flavours.</string>
    <string name="juice_description">Ingredients:\n (1 inch) fresh ginger root, peeled.\n 1 medium-sized pineapple.\n 2 cups water.\n 1 lime, juiced(optional).
        \n\n Method:\n 1. Remove peel and core from pineapple and chop into cubes.
        \n Then, start by peeling and roughly chopping the ginger, preparing these main ingredients for the juice.
    \n\n 2. Secondly, in a blender, pour 2 cups water, and simply blend the pineapple and ginger until all ingredients are pureed.
    \n\n 3. Pour juice through a strainer to get any remaining bits left.
    \n 4. Pour into a glass and serve immediately.</string>

    <string name="oat_name">Overnight Oats</string>
    <string name="oat_des">A sweet and gluten-free, chocolatey porridge, with hazelnut milk, berries, and chia seeds.</string>
    <string name="oat_description">Ingredients:\n 1 cup of Oats.\n 2tbps Chia seeds.\n Hazelnut milk.\n 1 tbps Cacao powder.\n Berries/Banana/fruit.
    \n\n Method:\n 1. In a bowl, place the oats, chia seeds and cacao powder and \n mix.
    \n 2. Pour nut milk till oats are covered.
    \n 3. Let it rest on the counter overnight, or place in fridge.
    \n 4. The following morning, stir mixture and add more milk to get the desired consistency.
    \n 5. Top with fruits of choice and enjoy!</string>

    <string name="lentil_name">Lovely Lentils</string>
    <string name="lentil_des">Protein-rich and filling lentil stew with mixed spices, peppers, red tomatoes, and freshly chopped coriander.</string>
    <string name="lentil_description">Ingredients:\n 250g Green/Lentils.\n 4/5 cloves of chopped Garlic.\n 2 medium chopped Onions.\n Handful of Coriander.
    \n Half a bell pepper.\n 1 chopped Tomato.\n 2tsps.Cumin.\n Salt.\n 1tbps Coconut oil.
    \n\n Method:\n 1. In a medium pot cook lentils till tender (about 30/40 minutes).
    \n\n 2. Whilst lentils are cooking, in a pan add coconut oil and fry garlic, onion,
    bell pepper, paprika, cumin and salt to taste till onions have become softened.
    \n\n 3. Add coriander to the pan.
    \n\n 4. Once lentils have been cooked, transfer pan mixture to pot and mix in with the lentils.
    \n\n 5. Enjoy with, plantain, rice or avocado.\n\n </string>

    <string name="soup_name">Soul Soup</string>
    <string name="soup_des">A warm and creamy tomato base, mixed with carrots, peppers, and good spices.</string>
    <string name="soup_description">Ingredients:\n Tomatoes.\n Carrots.\n 2 small onions.\n Red Pepper.
    \n Sea salt.\n 1 cup oats.\n Cumin.\n Garlic.\n Ginger.
    \n\n Method:\n 1. Put both tomatoes and carrots to boil in hot water. Wait 5 minutes until both
    tomatoes and carrots are soft and ready for peeling.
    \n\n 2. Once soft and ready, peel the ginger, onions, and garlic. Then chop into thin and tiny pieces
    including the red pepper.
    \n\n 3. Pour some olive oil in a frying pan and add the garlic, ginger, onions, and pepper.
    Then follow with adding a pinch of sea salt and cumin. Stir for 2 minutes.
    \n\n 4. Once ingredients fried, using a blender, place the fried ingredients as well as the boiled
    tomatoes/carrots in, and lastly 1 cup of oats. Mix all ingredients into blender.
    \n\n 5. Blend all the ingredients for about 5 minutes until smooth paste is formed.
    \n\n 6. Put smooth paste in a large frying bowl and stir/mix with spoon. Heat once again for 10 minutes.
    \n\n 7. Serve immediately and enjoy!\n\n</string>

    <string name="salad_name">Taco Salad</string>
    <string name="salad_des">A full taco salad with a range of delicious flavors and textures.</string>
    <string name="salad_description">Ingredients:\n Mushrooms.\n 2/3 Chopped garlic.\n 1 or 2 tbsp soya sauce.\n Olive oil.
    \n Sea salt.\n\n Salad:\n Cucumber.\n Red pepper.\n Fennel.\n Lime Juice.
    \n\n Method:\n 1.Heat the oil in a frying pan over a medium-high heat and add mushrooms
    garlic, 1tbsp soya sauce, and salt for taste.
    \n 2.Cook for 5-10mins until soft and cooked through.
    \n\n For the dressing: Season and stir in the cucumber, red pepper, and fennel.
    Scatter over lime juice and olive oil. Serve with ready made tortillas.\n</string>

    <string name="balls_name">Bliss Balls</string>
    <string name="balls_des">A small snack of date balls with cacao powder.</string>
    <string name="balls_description">Ingredients:\n 7/10 soaked/soft dates.\n 2/3 tbsps. Cacao powder.
    \n Any nut butter(peanut, almond, cashew etc.)\n Dash of salt.\n Dash of powdered cinnamon.
    \n\n Method:\n 1. In a processor, add all ingredients and pulse until well \n incorporated.
    \n 2. Using hands, form the balls approx. the same size.
    \n 3. Leave to rest in the fridge for 10 minutes.
    \n 4. Take out of fridge and Enjoy!</string>

    <string name="taco_name">Mini Tacos</string>
    <string name="taco_des">Satisfying mini-tacos with salad and avocado stuffing.</string>
    <string name="taco_description">Ingredients:\n 4/5 tortillas.\n 1 avocado.\n Juice of 1 and 2 cups a lemon.
    \n 2 tbsps. Olive oil.\n Hemp seeds.\n Wild rocket/lettuce/green of choice.
    \n Chopped cherry tomatoes (optional).\n\n Method:\n 1. In a pan, heat up tortillas.
        \n\n 2. Prepare in a bowl the "taco meat" by adding 1 smashed avocado, lemon
        juice, olive oil, hemp seeds, green of choice and cherry tomatoes(optional).
    \n\n 3. Scoop the "taco meat" to the tortilla and enjoy! </string>


</resources>
